

# HAKAN DAĞLI

# FRONT END DEVELOPER (ANGULAR - EXPERT)

COMPUTER ENGINEER

## CONTACT

tr.hakan.dagli@gmail.com

+90 507 542 0324

webpage

Ankara

/hakandagli

**in** hakandaglinet

# **EDUCATION**

**Suleyman Demirel University** 

Computer Engineer **3.14/4** 2017 - 2021

Mustafa Hakan Güvençer Science High School

Numerical Sciences **80.8/100** 2013 - 2017

# ADDIONAL INFORMATIONS

Country Turkey
Location Ankara
Birth Date 01/29/1999
Military Completed

• Driver License B

• Merital Status Single

# **ABOUT**

I am a Software Engineer with proven experience in ecommerce projects with tens of thousands of daily visitors, defense industry projects, and public and private sector projects. I have been using Angular on the front end for about four years. On the back end, I have approximately one year of experience with .NET Core.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer (Remote) MİA Teknoloji - Turkey 05.2024 - Currently

Front-End Developer (Remote)

NTT DATA Business Solutions Turkey - Japan 01.2023 - 04.2024

Full Stack Developer

ARKSOFT Bilişim - Turkey 10.2021 - 01.2023

Front-End Developer

Akıllı Sınav - Turkey 04.2021-09.2021

# **SKILLS**

## Front-End

- ANGULAR (v12-v19)
- Spartacus (SAP)
- HTML5
- CSS 3 / SCSS / SASS
- JavaScript (ES6,ES7)
- TypeScript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- PrimeNG

## Back-End

- .NET CORE
- MSSQL
- ENTITY FRAMEWORK

## **REFERANCES**

#### **Mehmet SERT**

NTT DATA - FE Team Lead

## Hüsamettin ELALMIŞ

ARKSOFT - Team Lead

### **Bedrettin SÜMER**

MİA Teknoloji- Team Lead

### **Ufuk Bora GÖZEN**

Akıllı Sınav - Co Founder

# **LANGUAGES**

- English
  - Reading B2
  - Speaking B1
  - Writing B1

# INDIVIDUAL PROJECTS

- arksoft.com.tr
- <u>esinavmerkezi.com</u>
- yurtoglukalip.com
- arksspr.com

# **HOBIES**

- Football Watching / Playing
- Off Road
- Camping
- Reading Leature
- Watching Movies, Series, Documentaries
- Body building

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## **MIA TEKNOLOJI**

# • MIA-MED Hospital Management System Software

- Contributed to the development of the web version of a hospital management system actively used in 9 cities in Turkey.
- Gained experience in **standalone component** architecture and **Signal-based programming** with **Angular 17**.
- Developed customized components with **PrimeNG** and designed dynamic, nested forms.
- Contributed to the infrastructure of a large-scale system with 1000+ screens, following the Angular Coding Style Guide.
- Designed a **scalable** architecture with **multi-theme** support.

### NTT DATA BUSINESS SOLUTIONS TURKEY

- SpeedyBunny.com Kuwait @
  - Developed a food ordering project actively used in Kuwait using the Angular-based Spartacus framework as part of SAP consultancy.
  - Optimized location-based services with Google Maps API.
  - Gained experience in multilingual application development by implementing Arabic language support and an RTLcompatible interface.

# • GRATIS.COM

- Developed with the Spartacus framework in this SAP-based e-commerce project.
- Worked on SEO improvements using Server-Side Rendering (SSR) and integrated GTM and CDN.
- Enhanced my reactive programming skills by managing complex data streams with RxJS.

### **ARKSOFT**

## EASY2PATCH

- Worked as a Front-End Developer on a project managing the latest versions of third-party applications used in both the public and private sectors.
- Optimized the file upload process by implementing chunked uploads to the API and improving the merging process on the front end.

### • ARKLICENSE

- Contributed as a **Full Stack Developer** to a customer and license management project, designing advanced tables and user interfaces with Angular & PrimeNG.
- Played an active role in critical processes like API design, data calculations, Azure AD integration, and Excel exports using MSSQL, .NET Core, and Entity Framework.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## • Session Audit

- Worked as a Front-End Developer on a project enabling secure session management and advanced reporting for shared machines at **ASELSAN** with Active Directory integration.
- Implemented **real-time data communication** using **SignalR** in Angular to display the live status of machines.

# • Exchange Device Management

- Worked as a Front-End Developer on the Exchange device management project.
- Developed a **boilerplate library** for use in various projects.

# **AKILLI SINAV**

## • Akıllı Sınav Education Module

• In this project, I used Angular and TypeScript to develop user-friendly interfaces, while utilizing Bootstrap for responsive design.